Hao Wang

No.6-1-302, XinWangLi Community, JINNAN District, Tianjin

■ (+86) 15665417757 | **■** whwendell@126.com

Personal Profile

A Master's graduate student at the Australian National University, undertaking the Machine Learning and Computer Vision program. Zealous about deep learning and machine learning and with 1+ years of work experience specializing in machine learning, convex optimization, deep graph networks and computer vision, python development, algorithms, and bioinformatics. Primarily, looking for a PhD opportunity to continue my research career.

Education

Australian National University

Canberra, Australia

MSc of Machine Learning and Computer Vision

July 2020 - July 2022

Hefei University of Technology

Hefei, China

Communication Engineering September 2014 - July 2018

University Projects

Metric Learning Algorithms in Person-identification

Hefei, China

Hefei University of Technology

February 2018 - June 2018

Thesis

Single Image Super-Resolution

Canberra, Australia

Australian National University

July 2020 - September 2020

• Technical Report: Siyuan Yan, Gefei Zhang, Hao Wang, Single Image Super-Resolution Using a Channel Attention Generative Adversarial Network.

Stress Recognition using thermal videos

Canberra, Australia

Australian National University

February 2021 - April 2021

• Publication: Hao Wang, Abhijit Adhikary. StressNet: A Deep Neural Network Based on Dynamic Dropout Layers for Stress Recognition. 28th International Conference on Neural Information Processing, 2021, Sanur, Bali, Indonesia.

Deep Declarative Networks

Canberra, Australia
February 2022 - June 2022

Australian National University

- Technical Report: Zhiwei Xu and Hao Wang, LESS: LEast Squares on Sphere for Iterative Energy Minimization and Novel Feature Representation.
- Technical Report: Hao Wang, Zhiwei Xu, and Stephen Gould, ViLESS: LEast Squares On Sphere For Video Classification.
- · Thesis: Least-squares on Sphere for Novel Feature Representation and Video Action Recognition.
- Publication: Zhiwei Xu, Hao Wang, Yanbin Liu, and Stephen Gould, PMaF: deep declarative layers for principal matrix features. International Conference on Machine Learning Workshop, Honolulu, Hawaii, USA, 2023.

Work Experience ____

Beijing E-Hualu Beijing, China

Software Engineer May 2018 - May 2019

- · Java and Python developer
- Technical Skills: Python with Django, Linux tools, Java, Spring Cloud, Git.

SOHU Beijing, China

Machine Learning Intern (got offer)

May 2021 - July 2021

• Technical Skills: Python with PyTorch, NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas, Scikit-learn, Setuptools, Wheel, Twine, Git.

ВіоМар

Beijing, China July 2021 -

Algorithm Engineer of Data Mining, High-Performance Computing Engineer

• Technical Skills: Deep graph networks, Transformers, Generative Models, Bioinformatics, CUDA, Denovo Protein Design using multi-objective optimization.

Skills

August 17, 2023

ProgrammingPython (Pandas, PyTorch, NumPy, Scikit-learn. etc.).MiscellaneousLinux, Shell (Bash/Zsh), LTEX(Overleaf/R Markdown), Git.Soft SkillsTime Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving.

AUGUST 17, 2023 2